hey spring fans in this installment of
嘿，春季粉丝
spring tip we're going to look at how to
春天的提示，我们将看看如何
build robust services services that do
建立功能强大的服务
the right thing even in the face of
即使面对
downstream service outages or failures
下游服务中断或故障
so let's go ahead and build a simple
因此，让我们继续构建一个简单的
application we're going to do this using
应用程序，我们将使用
a you know spring booting spring some
一个你知道春天引导春天一些
components from spring cloud
弹簧云中的组件
let's build a an application called the
让我们构建一个名为
robust client we're going to use Springs
强大的客户，我们将使用Springs
web support naturally we use actuator
网络支持我们自然使用致动器
we're going to use a retry the spring
我们将使用弹簧重试
retry library I'm going to use the
重试库，我将使用
Netflix hysterics circuit breaker okay
Netflix歇斯底里断路器好吗
now we'll hit generate but I don't want
现在我们点击生成，但是我不想
to just use the version of spring trial
只使用春季试用版
that we have on the clasp app so I'm
我们在扣式应用程序上拥有的
going to go ahead and instead add a
要继续，而是添加一个
preliminary version of spring we try to
春天的初步版本，我们尝试
our build this version is 1.2 rc1 this
我们建立的这个版本是1.2 rc1
version hasn't been released yet it's I
版本尚未发布，是我
mean it's it's that version itself is
就是说版本本身就是
released but it's not GA so we want to
已发布，但不是GA，因此我们要
take advantage of that ga unnhhh on GA
利用GA上的ga unnhhh
non GA code by going to our build and
转到我们的构建，然后查看非GA代码
changing the dependencies adding the
更改依赖项，添加
snapshot repositories the milestone
快照存储库是里程碑
repositories to our build and we want to
我们构建的存储库，我们想
promote by redefining a property we're
通过重新定义属性来促进
going to promote or you know bump up the
打算晋升，否则你就会知道
version of spring retry itself here to 1
春天版本重试到这里1
to 1 dot to do that are c1 and with that
到1个点即可做到c1和
we can build an application so let's
我们可以构建一个应用程序，所以让我们
let's go ahead and set the stage okay
让我们继续并设置好舞台
let's build an application called the
让我们构建一个名为
shaky business service okay and this is
摇摇欲坠的商务服务好，这是
going to this may potentially call some
去这个可能会叫一些
other you know web service right it'll
其他你知道的Web服务吧
be they'll call something else and do
他们会打电话给其他人做吗
something interesting so I want to do
一些有趣的事情，所以我想做
right we're going to derive some sort of
对，我们将得出某种
number we're not going to actually
我们实际上不会去的数字
bother calling another service because
麻烦打另一个服务，因为
we can just fake it right we can just
我们可以伪造它，我们可以
say if math dot random greater than 0.5
如果数学点随机数大于0.5
then we'll throw an exception let's
那我们就抛出一个异常
throw a new runtime exception signaling
抛出新的运行时异常信号
that something is wrong and when that
那是错的，什么时候
happens we'll also sleep so we'll
发生，我们也会睡觉，所以我们会
simulate a timeout if you will when we
如果您愿意，我们将模拟超时
call it down some service will sleep for
叫它一些服务会睡觉
3 seconds then it will quote you know
3秒钟，它将引用你知道的
add the exception accordingly otherwise
相应地添加异常
we'll just return 1 so if everything
我们只返回1，所以如果一切
goes fine we'll return 1 otherwise were
正常，我们将返回1，否则返回
well
好
call this down Jim service this
称这个为吉姆服务
fictitious service and something will go
虚构的服务，总有一天会发生
wrong and we want to be able to exercise
错误，我们希望能够锻炼
this potentially shaky service by
这项可能不稳定的服务
creating a rest controller so I'll say
创建一个休息控制器，所以我会说
shaky rest controller and our risk
不稳定的休息控制器和我们的风险
controller will take advantage of the
控制器将利用
newly created shaky business service
新创建的摇摇欲坠的商务服务
will reject that their create the
会拒绝他们创建
constructor at our wire here will say
我们在这里的接线员会说
this shaky business service equals shaky
这种摇摇欲坠的商业服务等于摇摇欲坠
business service and we're going to
商业服务，我们将
create an endpoint that's going to be
创建一个将要
exposed as public int boom and all we're
暴露于公共诠释热潮中，而我们
going to do is we're going to turn the
我们要做的是将
drive number if possible and we'll we'll
驱动器号（如果可能），我们将
deal with the exception so what'll
处理异常，那该怎么办
happen is if there is an exception right
发生是如果有例外权利
now that exception will get bubbled up -
现在该异常会冒出来-
spring MVC which will then report a it
春天的MVC，然后将报告它
should be HTTP status code 500 in
应该是HTTP状态码500
response so let's go ahead and try that
回应，让我们继续尝试
let's go ahead and see what we get just
让我们继续前进，看看我们得到了什么
for this okay we'll see it spin up on
为此，我们将看到它旋转起来
port 8080 zero I'm sorry 80 forward
端口8080零，对不起80转发
slash boom there it is okay it threw an
那里的砍伐热潮还可以
exception it timed out and it it bubbled
例外，它超时并冒泡
up to the spring MVC handler layer and
直到Spring MVC处理程序层和
we got the status code 500 that signals
我们得到了状态码500
that the server had a processing error
服务器出现处理错误
this is a generic error and our client
这是一个一般性错误，我们的客户
isn't going to know what to do with this
不会知道该怎么办
right it's better not to put that client
对，最好不要放那个客户
in the position in the first place
在第一的位置
instead we should handle it if we can
相反，如果可以的话，我们应该处理
and then potentially degrade gracefully
然后可能会优雅降级
we want to make sure that if there is
我们要确保如果有
something wrong that we do something
我们做某事的错
better than just propagating a big fat
比传播大量脂肪更好
Java stack trace or even more critically
Java堆栈跟踪或更重要的是
a nation should be status code like this
一个国家应该是这样的状态代码
to the client or potential iPhone client
给客户或潜在的iPhone客户
or an html5 JavaScript client for
或的html5 JavaScript客户端
example they're not gonna have any idea
例如，他们不会有任何想法
what to do with this so instead we know
该怎么办所以我们知道
let's introduce a fallback mechanism
让我们介绍一个后备机制
there's a few ways to do this one way of
有几种方法可以做到这一点
course I'm and I assume a lot of you
当然我是，我想你们很多
already know about this is we can use
已经知道这是我们可以使用
the Netflix hysterics circuit breaker
Netflix歇斯底里断路器
library and I have that on the classpath
库，我在类路径上
here this is spring cloud starter
这是春天的云启动器
histories
历史
and in order to activate it I just need
为了激活它，我只需要
to configure I need to activate the
配置我需要激活
circuit breaker there and you'd say that
那里的断路器，你会说
enable circuit breaker and then I
启用断路器，然后我
annotate my potentially shaky business
注释我可能不稳定的业务
logic here I annotated with at hystrix
我在hystrix注释的逻辑
command now this is actually a a
命令现在这实际上是一个
annotation from a third-party library
来自第三方库的注释
called Jovanka and japonica adapts the
名为Jovanka和japonica的
the underlying circuit breaker library
基础断路器库
to the spring component model and
弹簧组件模型
provide this nice annotation I'm not
提供这个不错的注释，我不是
really a big fan of having to call or
真的非常喜欢打电话或
tell it what to call using a string
告诉它使用字符串调用什么
right this is kind of ugly but but
对，这有点丑陋，但是
hystrix itself has a lot of benefits
hystrix本身有很多好处
right so what we're saying here is we
对，所以我们在这里说的是
want to call this fallback method it has
想调用它的后备方法
the same signature except for the name
除了名字外，签名相同
of course that has the same signature
当然具有相同的签名
and we're saying that we want to call
我们是说我们想打电话
that method and then return just two
该方法，然后只返回两个
instead of one so you know a lot of
而不是一个，所以你知道很多
high-performing websites will do this
高效能的网站会做到这一点
kind of thing they'll say oh well you
他们会说些好话的
went to the to the search engine service
前往搜寻引擎服务
and that's not available right now so
而且现在不可用，所以
instead here are some machine learned
相反，这里有一些机器学习
recommendations from across the web is
来自网络的建议是
it what you wanted no not quite but it's
它不是你想要的，但是
better than nothing right certainly so
总比没有好，所以肯定
that gives us some benefits now behind
现在给我们带来了一些好处
the scenes with actually happening is
实际发生的场景是
page tricks is creating what's called a
页面技巧正在创建所谓的
command object which is basically a
命令对象，基本上是一个
context it's a it's like a runnable but
上下文是一个可运行的，但是
it's a runnable that's managed within
在内部管理
this circuit breaker sort of context and
这种断路器的上下文和
the circuit breaker provides isolation
断路器提供隔离
in one of two different ways what we
以两种不同的方式之一，我们
want is to make sure that if this method
想要确保的是，如果此方法
goes off the rails if you throw if it
如果扔掉，它会脱离轨道
throws an exception that we don't run
抛出一个我们不运行的异常
the risk of permanently blocking for
永久封锁的风险
example or permanently losing our
例子或永久失去我们的
control of that thread so one way you
控制该线程的一种方式
can isolate a potentially shaky service
可以隔离潜在不稳定的服务
to service calls is to use an isolation
服务电话是使用隔离
mode called thread right and this is a
模式称为线程右，这是一个
configurable setting in the mystic
神秘中的可配置设置
circuit breaker that ends up creating a
最终导致产生的断路器
whole new thread every time you call a
每次调用一个新线程
method that uses the circuit breaker so
这样使用断路器的方法
it wraps this this method invocation
它包装了此方法调用
inside the body of a thread and that
在线程的主体之内
means that if you've got any kind of
表示如果您有任何一种
components that are using or relying
使用或依赖的组件
upon thread locals and there are a lot
在本地线程上，有很多
of them in your average your average
他们中的平均数
application
应用
or not right now you're trying to do
还是现在不尝试
manage transactions if you're trying to
如果您要管理交易
do
做
tracing if you're trying to do spring
追踪，如果你想做春天
security I mean there's all sorts of
安全，我的意思是有各种各样的
places where this gets hairy then you
那里毛茸茸的地方，然后你
need to know about that right that
需要知道那个权利
becomes a sort of a thing that's
变成一种东西
underneath your code that you may not
在您的代码下面，您可能不会
know about that
知道那件事
now can go wrong and it can it can go
现在可能会出错，它可以继续
wrong and very silent mysterious ways
错误和非常沉默的神秘方式
the other way to isolate things is to
隔离事物的另一种方法是
use semaphores this limits the number of
使用信号量，这限制了
threads that may be called it limits the
可以称为它的线程限制了
number of invocations that may be called
可以调用的调用数
by limiting the invocations to the
通过将调用限制为
semaphore whereas with a thread option
信号量，而带有线程选项
you limit the number of invocations that
您限制了调用的数量
may be called by limiting the number of
可以通过限制数量来调用
threads in the pool the you know they're
池中的线程，您知道它们是
they're trade offs the semaphore
他们权衡了信号量
approach is obviously much cheaper in
这种方法显然要便宜得多
terms of resource contingent and so on
资源条件等
it's not going to create a new thread
它不会创建一个新线程
for every damn tomb service on the other
为对方的每一次该死的坟墓服务
hand if you have something that may
手，如果你有可能
block forever and you know at this at
永远封锁，你知道这一点
the circuit breaker level there's no way
断路器级别没有办法
to like regain that there's no way for
想重新获得没有办法
the circuit breaker to just garbage
断路器只是垃圾
collect or weep that lost thread right
正确收集或哭泣丢失的线程
that may just go on forever
那可能永远持续下去
whereas if you are using the thread
而如果您正在使用线程
isolation that thread is managed by a
由线程管理线程的隔离
thread execute or a task execute or
线程执行或任务执行或
something like that right that's right
像这样的权利是正确的
cool and you can manage that more
很酷，您可以管理更多
explicitly you can you can destroy that
明确地，你可以摧毁它
off you know that sort of sine light
你知道那种正弦光
sideline process so the the choices are
副业过程，所以选择是
you know there's there's tension there
你知道那里有压力
there's a various various things you can
你可以有各种各样的事情
do to tune and finesse your performance
做调整和完善您的表现
characteristics it's ok good let's see
特点还可以，让我们来看看
what this looks like we've introduced
这是我们介绍的样子
the circuit breaker or restart it now
断路器或立即重启
I said they have to be the same
我说他们一定要一样
signature suppose I had a path variable
签名假设我有一个路径变量
swinging you see path variable here
摇摆你在这里看到路径变量
right for example path variable and I
例如路径变量和我
wanted to match a certain parameter in
想要匹配中的某个参数
the path I would have to declare the the
我必须声明的路径
string type there as well right even
甚至在那里的字符串类型
though this isn't supreme you see I have
尽管这不是至高无上的，你知道我有
the same identical identical parameters
相同相同相同参数
there so keep that in mind okay so
在那里，请记住这一点，好吧，所以
locals 8080 boom one okay fine now it
当地人8080繁荣现在可以了吗
looks like it's going to hesitate
看起来很犹豫
there's two so what happened was the
有两个所以发生了什么事
exception you know we got the the
例外，你知道我们得到了
shaky scoped block it hesitated for a
摇摇欲坠的范围块，犹豫了
second through an exception and we get
通过一个异常第二，我们得到
the circuit breaker so okay hesitation
断路器好犹豫
hesitation hesitation let's see if we
犹豫，犹豫，让我们看看是否
can call enough of these services here
可以在这里呼叫足够的这些服务
there you go now you see when I call
现在你去了，你看到我打电话时
number two when I call the endpoint now
我现在拨打端点时第二
it's going directly to two and it's not
它直接变成两个，而不是
hesitating anymore so one is what we get
犹豫了，所以我们得到的是
if everything is happy two is what we
如果一切都快乐，那么两个就是我们
get if there's a an exception right
获得是否有异常权利
that's the the fallback method but in
这是后备方法，但在
the very beginning when we call the
我们称呼之初
fallback method it would hesitate it
后备方法会很犹豫
first and eventually we got enough
首先，最终我们受够了
fallback methods that we'd see this stop
我们会看到此停止的后备方法
hesitating now it's going directly to
犹豫，现在直接
number two well it was this I can go
第二好，这是我可以去的地方
there let's see if we can yeah now it's
现在让我们看看是否可以
not even hesitating it's just going to
甚至毫不犹豫地只是
work into number two what's happened is
进入第二名发生了什么事
that the circuit breaker is no mere
断路器不仅仅是一个
try-catch block it's not just a fancy
try-catch块不仅花哨
way of doing a try-catch block it's
尝试捕获块的方法是
stateful it monitors the pathway sort of
有状态的它监视某种途径
between the the client and the
在客户端和客户端之间
downstream service
下游服务
it monitors the logic inside that
它监视其中的逻辑
circuit breaker and if it sees enough
断路器，如果看够了
successive attempts have failed it'll
连续的尝试都失败了
sort of switch the train tracks
切换火车轨道
directing traffic to the fallback
将流量引向后备
directly this gives our downstream
这直接给了我们下游
service time to recover so if you're
服务时间可以恢复，因此，如果您
calling a downstream service and that
打电话给下游服务
service isn't responding the last thing
服务没有回应最后一件事
you should be doing is to continue day
你应该做的是继续一天
losing it with requests while it's
在请求时丢失它
trying to recover so this gives that
试图恢复，所以这给了
downstream service time to breathe
下游呼吸时间
it gives it time to recover if you've
如果有的话，它有时间恢复
got something like Cloud Foundry Cloud
有类似Cloud Foundry Cloud之类的东西
Foundry will move heaven and earth all
铸造将使天地万物
day and all night
白天和整夜
to restart that service and it will
重新启动该服务，它将
eventually come back online when it does
最终在完成后重新联机
come back online we want to reintroduce
回来网上我们要重新介绍
traffic and so the circuit breaker has a
交通，因此断路器具有
reset timeout it it is going to attempt
重置超时它将尝试
to reintroduce traffic at if possible so
在可能的情况下重新引入流量
here you can see I've you know it timed
在这里你可以看到我知道你已经计时了
out I got the circuit breaker but you
出来我有断路器，但你
know I even if I trip the circuit
即使我跳开电路也知道我
breaker even if I open it eventually it
断路器，即使我最终将其打开
will reintroduce traffic and I was able
将重新引入流量，我能够
to go back to one so it's not
回到第一，所以不是
permanently set into that sort of switch
永久设置为这种开关
to track mode it can go back into the
跟踪模式，它可以返回到
main pathway as we'd expect now this is
我们现在期望的主要途径是
all very useful but I think one of the
都非常有用，但我认为其中之一
most interesting things about history
关于历史的最有趣的事情
isn't so much this behavior it's the
与其说是这种行为，不如说是
fact that you can MA
你可以MA的事实
you can you can observe it using the
您可以使用
hist explored you see every circuit
hist探索了您看到的每条电路
breaker provides a service and event
断路器提供服务和事件
heartbeat stream if you register the
如果您注册了心跳流
spring boot actuator in your class path
上课路线中的弹簧靴执行器
if you have that on the class path so
如果你在上课的路上有那个
here's history code stream it's an
这是历史代码流
actuator management in point this stream
执行器管理就是这一点
contains information about the the
包含有关的信息
circuit breaker the state of the circuit
断路器电路状态
breaker and you can use that for your
断路器，您可以将其用于您的
own purposes or you can plug it into
自己的目的，或者您可以将其插入
something called the his chicks
叫他的小鸡的东西
dashboard so let's do that it's kritis
仪表板，让我们这样做，这很严重
hurry hystrix dashboard here and we'll
在这里快点hystrix仪表板，我们将
use springs web support we use history
使用springs网站支持，我们使用历史记录
dashboard itself and we'll hit and
仪表板本身，我们将点击
generate open this up and I'm going to
产生打开这个，我要
run this application on a different port
在其他端口上运行此应用程序
right we want to run this on a different
对，我们要在其他位置运行
port because we've already got something
港口，因为我们已经有东西
running on port 8080 eighty right that's
在8080端口上运行，那是
our app so we'll say ad ten and we'll
我们的应用程序，所以我们说广告十，我们将
configure the history X dash board there
在此处配置历史记录X仪表板
and then that'll do so let's spin that
然后这样做，让我们旋转一下
up that'll spin spin up in Port a 10 and
向上旋转将在端口10中旋转并
what it's going to expect as its input
它期望什么作为输入
is this a service end event heartbeat
这是服务结束事件心跳吗
stream so localhost a 10 hystrix HTML
流所以本地主机的10 hystrix HTML
there we are paste it in there hit
在那里我们将其粘贴在那里
monitor and now you can see that as I
显示器，现在您可以看到
make requests on the Left the moving
向左移动请求
average on the right is going up it's
右边的平均值在上升
showing red whether it says 40% 43 %
显示红色是否表示40％43％
those are the number of requests that
这些是请求的数量
are getting through and then I have
正在通过，然后我有
errors by phone so 42 percent of the
电话错误，因此有42％
requests are failing that's roughly what
请求失败，大致就是
we expect right we said if it's roughly
我们期望是正确的，我们说的大概是
greater than half it'll it'll trip the
大于一半会跳闸
the exception eventually we get enough
最终我们得到足够的例外
successive attempts and you can see the
连续尝试，您可以看到
circuit is now open right so we can see
电路现已打开，所以我们可以看到
that reflected here something is wrong
反映出这里有问题
remember we can't change other people's
记住我们不能改变别人的
services we cannot add our
服务，我们无法添加我们的
instrumentation monitoring to their to
对其进行仪器监控
their systems all we can do is monitor
他们所能做的就是监控系统
the sort of ingress and egress ingress
进出的种类
and egress points in our application and
和我们应用程序中的出口点
monitor the flow of traffic from our
监控来自我们的流量
node to their nodes through the circuit
节点通过电路到达其节点
breaker that circuit breaker dashboard
断路器仪表板
in effect stands as a sort of monitoring
实际上是一种监视
for their service if the circuit breaker
为他们的服务，如果断路器
is open then we know that their service
是开放的，那么我们知道他们的服务
is down right
是正确的
this is very useful because now we have
这非常有用，因为现在我们有了
that sort of bird's-eye view at a glance
一览无余
sort of visibility naturally I've only
我自然只有一种可见性
got one circuit breaker one service
一台断路器一台
instance in one service at the moment
目前在一项服务中实例
but if I had more than one I would want
但是如果我不止一个，我会想要
to multiplex all of those circuit
多路复用所有这些电路
breakers into one screen and for this I
断路器进入一个屏幕，为此，我
could use spring cloud turbine which
可以使用弹簧云轮机
allows me to take all of the circuit
让我把所有的电路
breakers from all the different nodes in
来自所有不同节点的断路器
the system and sort of aggregate them
系统并对其进行汇总
into one stream which I could then plug
进入一个流，然后我可以插入
into this dashboard and I would have
进入这个仪表板，我将拥有
dozens or hundreds or thousands or
数十或数百或数千或
however many widgets all on one page for
但是许多小部件都在一页上
adding laps or comprehension alright so
加圈或理解力好吧
this is certainly one way to to achieve
这当然是实现的一种方法
what we're trying to do which is to
我们正在尝试做的是
introduce a little bit more robustness
引入更多的鲁棒性
in the code to make sure that if it's
在代码中，以确保是否
link goes wrong in the downstream
链接在下游出错
service we can do the right thing right
服务，我们可以做正确的事
but what I really want to talk to you
但是我真的想跟你说
about today is a is spring retry right
今天大约是春季重试
so spring retry is a different approach
所以春季重试是另一种方法
spring we try is a library that was
我们尝试的春天是一个图书馆
originally developed inside of spring
最初在春季内开发
batch and spring retry has been
批量和春季重试已
extracted out from spring backs as a
从回弹中提取出来的
separate library and it's used by lots
独立的图书馆，很多人都在使用
of different other projects so spring
春天不同的其他项目
batch of course spring cloud dataflow
当然这批春季云数据流
which you which uses spring batch spring
你用spring批处理哪个spring
integration and several other projects
整合和其他几个项目
in the spring ecosystem use spring retry
在春季生态系统中使用春季重试
so you know it's one of our most popular
所以你知道这是我们最受欢迎的之一
and most popularly downloaded libraries
以及最受欢迎的下载库
even if it's not necessarily a top-level
即使不一定是顶级的
project although if you're asking me I
项目，尽管如果你问我
think it really should be right it's a
认为真的应该是对的
very very useful library in of itself
本身非常非常有用的库
one of the new features one of the nice
新功能之一，尼斯
features in spring retry 1.20 rc1 and
spring retry 1.20 rc1和
and beyond you know soon to be GA is
而且不知道您即将成为GA
support for a circuit breaker so let's
支持断路器，让我们
look at the circuit breaker let's look
看一下断路器，让我们看一下
at spring we try it without the circuit
在春天，我们尝试不带电路
breaker first of all and then we'll look
首先是断路器，然后我们来看
at how to turn on the circuit breaker
在如何打开断路器
functionality so here's our fallback
功能，这是我们的后备
method and here's our potentially shaky
方法，这是我们潜在的不稳定
service to service call we're going to
服务到服务电话，我们将
go ahead and enable spring retries so
继续进行春季重试，这样
we'll say at enable retry and my
我们会在启用重试中说
expectation of course is that most
当然，期望是
people going to consume this stuff from
人们打算从那里消费这些东西
spring boots so this is all you need and
spring boot ，这就是您所需要的，
then we have here the same kind of thing
那么我们这里有同样的事情
you have a
你有一个
we travel right and here we're going to
我们旅行正确，这里我们要
say that we want to include a certain
说我们要包括某个
exception right if we don't include
如果我们不包括例外权
anything then all exceptions will be
任何事情，所有例外都会
will be
将会
we will trigger we try and here we have
我们将触发我们尝试，在这里我们有
a trick cover right and what we expected
一个技巧把戏和我们期望的
to pass here is our is the type of
通过这里是我们的类型
exception we want to handle so I could
我们想处理的异常，所以我可以
just leave it as is and and decide to
只是保持原样，然后决定
handle runtime exception right yes and I
是的，我可以处理运行时异常
can blog the exception there so this
可以在这里博客例外，这样
gets paired they get matched right in if
配对，如果他们匹配
this method throws an exception then
该方法将引发异常
this method gets invoked as the as sort
此方法作为as调用
of the recovery Handler now let's create
现在，让我们创建恢复处理程序
a custom exception just to be very
自定义例外
specific to demonstrate some the
具体来展示一些
configuration so we'll say boom
配置，所以我们说繁荣
exception extends runtime exception and
异常扩展了运行时异常，并且
we're going to override the constructor
我们将覆盖构造函数
here passing in a string and it will say
在这里传递一个字符串，它会说
that we want to include boom exception
我们想包括繁荣例外
so that's going to be just this
所以就是这样
exception all the other exceptions will
所有其他例外
trigger a 500 status code it'll bubble
触发500状态代码
up to a the spring MVC layer and we'll
直到春季MVC层，我们将
see that reflected so boom exception and
看到这反映了繁荣景象，
over here we have a generic sort of we
在这里，我们有一种通用的
have our generic fall through method and
让我们的通用方法失败并
we can leave it as a runtime exception
我们可以将其保留为运行时异常
or we can be very specific and and sort
或者我们可以非常具体和分类
of handle only this particular type of
只处理这种特定类型的
exception and we can have multiple
例外，我们可以有多个
recover methods in the same component
恢复同一组件中的方法
right it doesn't really matter now just
对吧，现在真的不重要了
as with a circuit breaker with a history
就像有历史的断路器一样
circuit breaker rather the signature has
断路器而不是签名
to match so we have this you know we
匹配，所以我们有这个，你知道我们
have both of these as we did before
像我们以前一样拥有这两个
let's go ahead and restart this now this
让我们继续并重新启动这个
is just retry ability right this is not
只是重试能力，这不是
as smart as a circuit breaker it doesn't
像断路器一样聪明
it doesn't keep enough state to then
它没有保持足够的状态
permanently sort of route the train
火车的永久路线
tracks to the downstream service it'll
跟踪到下游服务
always attempt to call the service and
始终尝试致电服务，
then if it fails it'll it'll retry so
然后如果失败，它将重试，因此
let's see what that looks like
让我们看看看起来像什么
here we go exception its fail
在这里，我们去异常失败
it's trying multiple times to call that
它试图多次调用
service and we're waiting for the
服务，我们正在等待
response to eventually come through so
最终通过这样的回应
if it doesn't if it's not able to try
如果没有，如果不能尝试
it's not able to get the result enough
它无法获得足够的结果
times we'll see that it'll eventually
次，我们将看到它最终
call the fallback so let's use a logger
调用后备广告，让我们使用记录器
here actually I can just print out
实际上我可以在这里打印出来
calling a drive number okay we'll add
拨打驱动器号码好吧，我们将添加
that to the output there or restart so
到那里的输出或重新启动，所以
now as it as it calls the the method
现在，因为它调用了方法
which should see it being retried
应该看到它被重试
multiple times this is ideal for things
多次，这是理想的东西
that are identical
一样的
calling the right number see I'm not
拨打正确的号码，看看我不是
invoking it it's just printing out in
调用它只是在打印出来
the console and eventually it gives up
控制台，最终它放弃了
but it eventually makes it either gifts
但最终还是成为礼物
with successful result or it times out
结果成功或超时
we get the the fallback method so there
我们得到了后备方法，所以
we are
我们是
everything seems to be fine now it's
一切似乎都很好，现在
doing it again I haven't touched the
再做一次，我没有碰过
keyboard it's just invoking it three
键盘只是调用它的三个
times in succession or several times in
连续几次或多次
succession for us so this is the
对我们的继承，所以这是
standard behavior of spring wheat rice
春小麦饭的标准行为
spring wheat right does not have the
春小麦对没有
ability to isolate things based on
隔离事物的能力
semaphores or threads yet but I would
信号量或线程，但我会
argue that's actually you know not not
认为实际上你不知道
really a problem because we can use at a
确实有问题，因为我们可以在
sink for example and you can use at a
例如水槽，您可以在
sink this is a annotation that spinning
下沉这是旋转的注释
Springs in spring 3.1 and basically when
春天在春天3.1和基本上什么时候
you add this to a method it it invokes a
您将此添加到它调用一个方法
method inside of a thread pool so you
线程池中的方法，这样您
can say at enable at a sink specify a
可以说在启用接收器时指定一个
task executor and then this just gets
任务执行器，然后得到
this just works and now you have more
这样就可以了，现在您还有更多
explicit control and you can see that
显式控制，您可以看到
there's going to be some sort of sort of
将会有某种形式的
thread logic in your code that you know
您知道的代码中的线程逻辑
it's very much a service level concern
这非常关注服务水平
now you're aware of it the other thing
现在你知道了另一件事
is that we haven't really enjoyed the
是我们真的不喜欢
same sort of circuit breaker like
一样的断路器
functionality right so we actually need
功能正确，所以我们实际上需要
to we're going to we're going to go
我们要去
ahead and take advantage now over of a
提前利用现在的优势
new feature in spring we try called the
春天的新功能，我们尝试称为
circuit breaker and I expect that this
断路器，我希望这
circuit breaker annotation will be sort
断路器注释将排序
of integrated with the at enable circuit
与at使能电路集成
breaker annotation instead of spring
断路器注释而不是弹簧
trial
试用
eventually so that way you can choose
最终，这样您就可以选择
choose either hystrix or to use spring
选择hystrix或使用spring
we try and they'll both be activated
我们尝试，它们都会被激活
activated by using a table circuit
通过表电路激活
breaker just like we did with history's
就像我们对历史所做的那样
but in our case the only thing that we
但就我们而言，我们唯一的
need to change is circuit breaker itself
需要改变的是断路器本身
and you know everything else is very
你知道其他所有的事情
much the same we have different
差不多，我们有不同
parameters here the reset timeout is
此处的参数复位超时为
it's basically 20,000 milliseconds that
基本上是20,000毫秒
means it's going to wait 20 seconds
表示要等待20秒
before it attempts to reintroduce
在尝试重新引入之前
traffic right so we'll say we'll just
交通顺畅，所以我们会说我们只是
leave it as it is actually that's fine
离开它，因为这实际上很好
so let's go ahead and hit the circuit
所以让我们继续前进
breaker this circuit breaker provides
该断路器提供的断路器
everything that we need
我们需要的一切
except for that disturbance and event
除了那个干扰和事件
heartbeat stream right so I like this
心跳流正确，所以我喜欢这个
and I think it's a much cleaner model to
我认为这是一种更清洁的模型
to design recover methods in terms of
从以下方面设计恢复方法
the exception types than to design it
异常类型比设计异常
using these sort of string lis type
使用这类字符串lis类型
annotations specification so here we go
注释规范，所以我们开始
it's calling the downstream service
叫下游服务
hesitating stuttering stuttering calling
犹豫不决
calling stuttering there we go
叫口吃我们去
now you can see it's calling the
现在您可以看到它正在调用
downstream service it's going directly
下游服务，直接进行
to number two it's going directly to the
第二，它直接进入
the fallback because you know it's it's
后备，因为你知道它是
a circuit breaker now right it's doing
现在正在做的断路器
the same kind of thing as as our history
和我们的历史一样
circuit breaker is doing so this is very
断路器正在这样做，这非常
convenient you know in in in practical
在实践中您知道的便利
terms they are functionally equivalent I
术语，它们在功能上是等效的
think except for the service and event
考虑服务和事件
heartbeat stream I have it on good
心跳流我很好
authority that building that stroke
权威，以建立中风
circuit breaker you know service an
您知道的断路器
event heartbeat stream in a way that
事件心跳流以某种方式
would be compatible with the historic
与历史兼容
status board shouldn't be too hard so
状态板不应该太难，所以
maybe we'll see that make an appearance
也许我们会看到出现
before GA who knows either way I
在GA之前，我都知道
encourage you to go out and grab the
鼓励你出去抓
bits kick the tires and have fun
踢轮胎，玩得开心
building services that do the right
建立正确的服务
thing in the face of service outages and
面对服务中断的事情
failures
失败
you
您